[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Arsenic poisoning mainly disrupts this system.", "correct_answer": "Digestive system", "incorrect_answers": ["Cardiovascular system", "Endocrine system", "Nervous system"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "An old adage states, Neurotics build castles in the sand. Psychotics live in them.  Which one of the following disorders is not considered a neurosis?", "correct_answer": "Schizoid Personality Disorder", "incorrect_answers": ["Obsessive-Compulsive Disorder", "Panic Disorder", "Agoraphobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What nickname did the priest and the cemetery gardener give to Ned, the dog in the 2007 suspense movie The Number 23?", "correct_answer": "The Guardian of the Dead", "incorrect_answers": ["The Nightmare", "The Spectral Dog", "The Devils Pooch"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where was most of the filming of the 2009 movie The Ugly Truth done?", "correct_answer": "California", "incorrect_answers": ["New York", "Florida", "Paris"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not among the traditional ingredients used for the preparation of the Arab dish Matbucha?", "correct_answer": "Lamb meat", "incorrect_answers": ["Tomato", "Bell paper", "Garlic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This country has more Internet Service Providers than any other non-English speaking country.", "correct_answer": "Czech republic", "incorrect_answers": ["Russia", "Romania", "Brazil"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What phenomenon, observed near the North Pole, is caused by the interaction between solar winds and the Earths magnetic field?", "correct_answer": "Northern lights", "incorrect_answers": ["Earthquakes", "Solar eclipse", "Tides"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Whose real name was Leonard Sly?", "correct_answer": "Roy Rogers", "incorrect_answers": ["Leonardo DiCaprio", "Gerald Ford", "Leonard Nimoy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ichthyology is a branch of biology that deals with which of these?", "correct_answer": "Fish", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Amphibians", "Water animals"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did William Kolb invent the first red candy apple?", "correct_answer": "1908", "incorrect_answers": ["1914", "1910", "1921"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During what year did Samuel Morse come up with the idea of Morse Code?", "correct_answer": "1838", "incorrect_answers": ["1848", "1818", "1828"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the line, which is the same distance from the North Pole and South Pole and runs horizontally around the world.", "correct_answer": "Equator", "incorrect_answers": ["Tropic of Capricorn", "Tropic of Cancer", "Prime Meridian"]}]